{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"7394/23",
			"answer":"7394/23",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6929/49",
			"answer":"6929/49",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2093/17",
			"answer":"2093/17",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9169/42",
			"answer":"9169/42",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4937/23",
			"answer":"4937/23",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"39.69/4.9",
			"answer":"39.69/4.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.672/7.3",
			"answer":"4.672/7.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"103.4/1.1",
			"answer":"103.4/1.1",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"960/12",
			"answer":"960/12",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.0837/27",
			"answer":"0.0837/27",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}